<mapdescription author="Damo" public="0">
    <description language="en">
        <mapname>Expedition - Cutscene 2</mapname>
        <description>&#x0A;Mora is a god no more - The Sundbridge Shrine was cleansed of the twilight&apos;s curse and Mora&apos;s minions have been defeated. &#x0A;But the star trapped in the heart of the earth, which the shrine connected to its brother in the boundless void, had already been tainted with the curse of twilight. &#x0A;The worst outgrowth of this new infestation has affected a fire tribe in a distant land in the south, a tribe that worships the molten core.  &#x0A;It was not long before the curse spread beyond the tribe&apos;s members and plunged the whole land into darkness. &#x0A;A group of brave lyrish volunteers undertook an expedition south to nip this new outbreak in the bud. &#x0A;</description>
    </description>
    <description language="de">
        <mapname>Expedition - Cutscene 2</mapname>
        <description>&#x0A;Mora ist kein Gott mehr - Der Sonnensteg-Schrein wurde vom Zwielichtfluch befreit und Moras Schergen wurden besiegt.&#x0A;Aber der im Herzen der Erde gefangene Stern, den der Schrein mit seinem Bruder in der grenzenlosen Leere verband, war bereits mit dem Fluch des Zwielichts behaftet.&#x0A;Die schlimmste Auswüchse dieser neuen Plage hat einen Feuerstamm in einem fernen Land im Sueden getroffen, einen Stamm, der den geschmolzenen Kern verehrt. &#x0A;Es es dauerte nicht lange, bis sich der Fluch über die Mitglieder des Stammes ausbreitete und das ganze Land in Dunkelheit stürzte.&#x0A;Obwohl sie gerade erst ihr eigenes Land von diesem FLuch befreiten, unternahm eine Gruppe tapferer, lyrischer Freiwilliger eine Expedition in den Sueden, um diesen neuen Ausbruch im Keim zu ersticken.&#x0A;</description>
    </description>
    <description language="fr">
        <mapname>Expedition - Cutscene 2</mapname>
        <description></description>
    </description>
    <description language="ru">
        <mapname>Expedition - Cutscene 2</mapname>
        <description></description>
    </description>
</mapdescription>
